etype.com 2017-11-18

# eType Privacy Policy

**1\. Your Privacy Policy**  
1.1. At eType we recognize that privacy is important to you. This Privacy Policy applies to all eType Services.  
1.2. If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at our contact page.  
**2\. Definitions**  
2.1. Any and all terms and definitions used herein shall have the same meaning as set forth in the Terms of Use unless otherwise indicated herein.  
2.2. In this Privacy Policy the following capitalized definitions are being used, singular as well as plural.  
3\. Information we collect and how we use it  
3.1. At eType we collect only limited information on you. Using eType Services does not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information, however you may give us your e-mail address to receive certain communications from us (such as newsletters). Other than to the extent detailed under this Privacy Policy, we do not request nor collect any other personal data on you.  
3.2. When you use the Services, unidentifiable, non-personal statistical data is sent to eType in order to help us improve the Services and our product support. Such non-personal data may include the count of clicks on our Services components and unidentifiable queries. Such statistical data is not associated with the limited personal data we acquire.  
3.3. eType may share the statistical data with its advertisers and business partners. Such data is used to help the advertisers and business partners improve and enrich their services and support. eType does not otherwise share personal information about a user with any third party, unless doing so is necessary to protect the legal rights of eType or any third party. We may also disclose your personal identifying information to third parties if we are required to do so by law.  
**4\. Website privacy**  
While you visit our Website or use the Software online, we collect limited information that your browser makes available, such as URL, IP address, browser type and the characteristics of your queries, such as time and dates. We use your IP address to improve our Services, help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic information.  
**5\. Links**  
eType Services may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that eType is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such other websites and that entering or using such websites is at your own risk. You are responsible to read, as you enter such websites and prior to any use thereof, the privacy statements of each and every such website. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by eType.  
**6\. Cookies**  
We may set and access cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies in a limited way to track usage on our Website. We gather information about the Website use by our Website users through cookie technology on an anonymous basis and analyze it at an aggregate level only. This enables us to continually improve our Website to meet the needs of our users.  
**7\. Information security**  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized Access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store our limited personal data.  
**8\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
8.1. eType reserves the right to update the Privacy policy at any time without notice to you.  
8.2. Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.  
**9\. Subordination to the Terms of Use.**  
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms and conditions of the Terms of Use, as an integral part thereof; in case of a contradiction between any provision of the Terms of Use, and the content of the Terms of Use shall govern.
